So because of the government shutdown, SNAP benefits are basically not going to be fulfilled
for the month of November. And food pantries are going to be a really important go-to for folks.
I just collabed with a brother about this earlier today. However, what I'm seeing in the comments
is a lot of commentary about food pantries that I think a lot of people may not know because I know
I didn't. So if you have ever had to frequent food pantries, if you frequent them now, if you work at
a food pantry, can you please in the comments tell us what is the best way to be helpful and useful
to food pantries? Is it donating like dollars? Is it donating actual items? If you are somebody
who has frequented or is frequenting a food pantry, what do they never have that you actually want?
Because I think, you know, the other part of this too is that people kind of just don't acknowledge
the fact that like, just because you probably don't mean you don't have preferences. So I would
love to get those specificities because I want to be able to help at the food pantry that's around my
way. And I would love to hear like, what are the things that folks be wanting that aren't never,
that aren't typically provided. Also, once I have my book door, my book tour dates, I'm going to want
to connect with organizations that are in those towns to figure out how we can also use my book tour
dates for mutual aid opportunities. So, you know, coupling the book dates with drives, right? So for
instance, like when I did stand up, I would do different drives or voter registration drives. We're not
doing that this time. But like, I remember in Detroit, the time that the Zionists tried to
cancel my show, we did a shoe drive for the Congo for the Interbenera Foundation, because when you
donate them shoes, they send the shoes to the Congo where folks don't be having shoes and you need to
have shoes because there's so much bacteria and issues that happen through just not having shoes.
Anyways, the point is, keep a lookout for that if you are an organization that does mutual aid,
because I'm going to want to partner with you to see how we can harness the audience that's coming
to buy my book and sign my book to also be involved in mutual aid in their community.
I believe that if white folks do not build altars on Juneteenth, they should be haunted.